ELIJAH OKEOWO

Contact

Address:

100 Pipeline street, Ijede, Ikorodu, Lagos, Nigeria.

Phone:

+234 8151267997

Email:

elijah.okeowo01@gmail.com

Languages

English – A1 Yoruba – B2

Summary

Dependable social media manager that specializes in the creation of social media pages across various social media platforms, and ensuring the growth of all managed pages with the right audience. Also experienced in creation of contents which includes egraphics and videos, for engagement purposes on the managed pages.

Skill Highlights

- Content Creation
- Social media management
- Facebook ADs
- Digital marketing
- Google ADs
- SEO
- Community
 Management

Experience

SOCIAL MEDIA MANAGER – 06/2020 till date **DYNA MEDIA,** Nigeria

CONTENT CREATOR - 06/2020 till date **DYNA MEDIA,** Nigeria

SOCIAL MEDIA MANAGER – 18/10/2022 to 01/12/2022 **TABOK Schools**, Nigeria

SOCIAL MEDIA MANAGER – 21/11/2021 to 27/03/2022 **MFM YOUTH CHURCH (IJEDE),** Nigeria

Education

Bachelor of Science: **Computer Science** – (2018 – 2022), **Hallmark University**, Ogun state, Nigeria.

Certifications

COMMUNITY MANAGEMENT, DIGITAL MARKETING, CONTENT CREATION, GOOGLE ANALYTICS, GRAPHICS DESIGN.